including in suspect which was the first
to have a live feed of grapes from the
workshop being you know providing
instant clean survey process to our
customers so along with this you had so
many other firsts uh we continue to
strive for Innovation and to be the
number one across technology across
products and across services
this is just a snapshot of the products
that we are going to talk about in the
next section in health in motor and
corporate we're talking about a total of
protein products and you will see that
IT addresses various customer segments
various customer needs and also a huge
uh you know fill up to technology and
customer being the center of all our
services
talking about health insurance
as the first segment let me first tell
you our philosophy and vision as far as
health is concerned we believe that we
want to grow the health insurance space
as a custodian of care
the idea is that we just don't want to
be a pair of claims but we want to
partner people in their head Journey
because we believe that is customers
remain healthy and they can take care of
their health
you know our portfolio remains healthy
we are able to sustain this portfolio
over a long period of time and that
helps us in ensuring that the premiums
customer paid in the in their long-term
association with us are kept under
control
so we don't want to simply be somebody
who's paying claims then you know a
hospitalization happens we want to be
proactive we want to ensure that we
provide services that you know start
from the wellness of customers so so
that those who are healthy remain
healthy those who are turning to be say
unhealthy we can help them to either
come back to their health or at least
sustain so they don't they don't become
chronic and if in in case they become
chronic we ensure that we provide them
services on outpatient or Diagnostics on
second opinion so that